{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which is the most popular JavaScript framework?",
      "options": [
        "Angular",
        "React",
        "Svelte",
        "Vue"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which company invented React?",
      "options": [
        "Google",
        "Apple",
        "Netflix",
        "Facebook"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the fundamental building block of React apps?",
      "options": [
        "Components",
        "Blocks",
        "Elements",
        "Effects"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the name of the syntax we use to describe the UI in React components?",
      "options": [
        "FBJ",
        "Babel",
        "JSX",
        "ES2015"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How does data flow naturally in React apps?",
      "options": [
        "From parents to children",
        "From children to parents",
        "Both ways",
        "The developers decides"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How to pass data into a child component?",
      "options": [
        "State",
        "Props",
        "PropTypes",
        "Parameters"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "When to use derived state?",
      "options": [
        "Whenever the state should not trigger a re-render",
        "Whenever the state can be synchronized with an effect",
        "Whenever the state should be accessible to all components",
        "Whenever the state can be computed from another state variable"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What triggers a UI re-render in React?",
      "options": [
        "Running an effect",
        "Passing props",
        "Updating state",
        "Adding event listeners to DOM elements"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "When do we directly \"touch\" the DOM in React?",
      "options": [
        "When we need to listen to an event",
        "When we need to change the UI",
        "When we need to add styles",
        "Almost never"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "In what situation do we use a callback to update state?",
      "options": [
        "When updating the state will be slow",
        "When the updated state is very data-intensive",
        "When the state update should happen faster",
        "When the new state depends on the previous state"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "If we pass a function to useState, when will that function be called?",
      "options": [
        "On each re-render",
        "Each time we update the state",
        "Only on the initial render",
        "The first time we update the state"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which hook to use for an API request on the component's initial render?",
      "options": [
        "useState",
        "useEffect",
        "useRef",
        "useReducer"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which variables should go into the useEffect dependency array?",
      "options": [
        "Usually none",
        "All our state variables",
        "All state and props referenced in the effect",
        "All variables needed for clean up"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "An effect will always run on the initial render.",
      "options": [
        "True",
        "It depends on the dependency array",
        "False",
        "In depends on the code in the effect"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "When will an effect run if it doesn't have a dependency array?",
      "options": [
        "Only when the component mounts",
        "Only when the component unmounts",
        "The first time the component re-renders",
        "Each time the component is re-rendered"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    }
  ],
  "cities": [
    {
      "cityName": "Lisbon",
      "country": [
        "Portugal",
        "pt"
      ],
      "emoji": "pt",
      "date": "2027-10-31T15:59:59.138Z",
      "notes": "My favorite city so far!",
      "position": {
        "lat": 38.727881642324164,
        "lng": -9.140900099907554
      },
      "id": 73930385
    },
    {
      "cityName": "Madrid",
      "country": [
        "Spain",
        "es"
      ],
      "emoji": "es",
      "date": "2027-07-15T08:22:53.976Z",
      "notes": "",
      "position": {
        "lat": 40.46635901755316,
        "lng": -3.7133789062500004
      },
      "id": 17806751
    },
    {
      "cityName": "Berlin",
      "country": [
        "Germany",
        "de"
      ],
      "emoji": "de",
      "date": "2027-02-12T09:24:11.863Z",
      "notes": "Amazing ðŸ˜ƒ",
      "position": {
        "lat": 52.53586782505711,
        "lng": 13.376933665713324
      },
      "id": 98443197
    },
    {
      "cityName": "Nijar",
      "country": [
        "Spain",
        "es"
      ],
      "emoji": "es",
      "date": "2023-04-03T07:47:59.202Z",
      "notes": "",
      "position": {
        "lat": "36.967508314568164",
        "lng": "-2.13128394200588"
      },
      "id": 98443198
    }
  ],
 "services": [
    {
      "name": "Web Development",
      "description": "Front-end developer, I transform the UI/UX design into Projects by using technologies like HTML,CSS, JAVASCRIPT and their Third-party libraries such as React JS and Tailwind CSS, Transform projects into Functional, Interactive Websites that deliver Exceptional Performance.",
      "icon": "FaLaptopCode"
    },
    {
      "name": "Integration with Back-end",
      "description": "Communicate and Integrate with back-end services by using the most common way APIs (Application Programming Interfaces) to fetch data, submit forms and perform other operations.",
      "icon": "FaCodeBranch"
    },
    {
      "name": "User Experience Optimization",
      "description": "Creating a positive and seamless experience for users, Improve the user experience based on user feedback and  analytics, ensuring that the application meets the needs and expectations of its users.",
      "icon": "MdOutlineSettingsSuggest"
    },
    {
      "name": "User Interface Design",
      "description": "Designing user interfaces that are visually appealing, intuitive to use, and aligned with the brand identity of the application, Responsive Design and optimal user experience across all devices screens, Interactive Features such as Animations, transitions, and real-time updates to enhance the user experience.",
      "icon": "LuLayoutDashboard"
    }
  ],
  "process": [
    {
      "name": "Request Project",
      "description": "It all starts with your project request. I listen carefully to understand what you need and your ideas. Your ideas are my inspiration, and understanding your goals is my top priority."
    },
    {
      "name": "Ideation",
      "description": "In this step, creativity takes center stage. I delve into brainstorming sessions to conceptualize your project. This is where I explore innovative solutions and artistic approaches to bring your vision to life."
    },
    {
      "name": "Designing",
      "description": "With a clear concept in mind, we move to the design phase. This is where I weave together visual elements, user-friendly interfaces, and all the creative components that will make your project stand out."
    },
    {
      "name": "Feedback",
      "description": "Your feedback is invaluable. I present the design work to you for your input. I'm dedicated to collaboration and will make revisions as necessary to ensure the final product aligns perfectly with your artistic vision."
    },
    {
      "name": "Launch",
      "description": "After your approval, it's time to release your project to the world. I handle all the technical details, ensuring a seamless launch. Your project is introduced to the public, where it will inspire and engage."
    }
  ]
}
